Hasan Can Çelik

Q github.com/HasanCan6241 in HasanCan ■ hasancan.celik6241@gmail.com ♀ Tunceli, Turkey • 05300894963

PROFILE

I have gained experience in both individual and team projects throughout my educational career. I manage my projects using Agile methodology and have a passion for artificial intelligence and machine learning. I am actively developing myself in big data, data preprocessing, machine learning, deep learning, and data analysis

EDUCATION

Fırat University

August 2020 - July 2024

Software Engineering AGNO: 3,49

For my graduation project, I successfully completed a web-based artificial intelligence project capable of detecting brain tumors, skin cancer, and diabetes diseases.

WORK EXPERIENCE

Intellium | Data Scientist Intern

26 February 2024 - 14 June 2024

I developed an innovative artificial intelligence-supported, web-based project for Intellium company to be used in their recruitment processes.

Information Technology Department | Data Scientist Intern

4 September 2023 - 29 September 2023

I contributed to data-driven decision-making processes by working on data manipulation, data analysis, data visualization, and artificial intelligence models.

Innovance Consultancy | Artificial Intelligence Developer Intern

18 July 2022 - 19 August 2022

I have worked on data preprocessing, data analysis, data visualization, artificial neural networks, and machine learning algorithms.

PROJECTS

Improving the Sensory Skills of Children with Autism with AR Technology | AR, Unity

- Our project, which we submitted under TÜBİTAK 2209-A 2023 2nd Term, and for which I am the project leader, has been awarded funding
- Using AR technology, we aimed to enhance the educational processes of autism children, making their learning experiences more effective and supportive

Artificial Intelligence Supported and Web Based Recruitment Platform | Python, Flask, SQL Server, Scikit-learn, NLTK

- I developed a web-based application for companies to use in their recruitment processes
- I developed a model that calculates the suitability of candidates applying to the company's job openings based on the positions they applied for
- I performed data analysis and visualization processes to thoroughly analyze and understand candidate data

Artificial Intelligence Supported Web Application for Brain Tumor Diagnosis and Treatment Planning | GPT

- I developed an application that can detect and classify brain tumors based on uploaded MRI images
- I developed a model that performs personalized treatment planning in case of tumor detection

SKILLS

Python, SQL, HTML/CSS, Pandas, NumPy, Scikit-learn, TensorFlow, Keras, NLTK, Power BI, Matplotlib, Seaborn, Plotly, Folium, Flask, Django, Scrapy, BeautifulSoup, Data Preprocessing, Data Modeling, Statistics, Data Visualization, NLP, Sentiment Analysis

LANGUAGES

Turkish: Native Languages English: B1(İntermediate)